रूठी है शब्द रब्बा रब्बा दिल भी है रूठा सब कुछ है बिखरा बिखरा बिखरा सारू ठारूठा चिपनाइ चुप है लांजाल मोल कैसे वे लाजा मोल कैसे वे आ जा आ जा
系列
म्यूसिक नहीं चुप कर आ जा जा म्यूसिक
मेरा लोराया खैर तुम फिक्र मत करो मैंने कहा ना मैं सब संभाल लूँगा
लव
तुम कितने अच्छे हो
मेरा कितना ध्यान रखते हो मुझे कितना प्यार करते हो ये जानते हुए भी की मैं देख नहीं सकती मैं अंधी हूँ मेरा घर संभाले हो मेरा ऑफिस सँभालते हो और मुझे हर तरह से कितना सपोर्ट करते हो थैंक यू सो मच अरे इसमें थैंक यू की क्या बात
है दोनों अलग थोड़ी है तुम्हारा बिज़नेस मैं नहीं संभालूंगा तो कौन संभालेगा
चलो तुम्हारे लिए फाइनल लेके आता हूँ बैठो
मैं तुम्हारे लिए फाइनल लेके आता हूँ
My name is doctor James
I'm the eye specialist
it's our first time so don't worry I'm a friend of your husband
OK if you're ready let's head into the clinic
Please have a seat
Sorry but your husband will have to wait outside
I need to focus on my patient oh OK
thank you
OK zombies so how long have you not been feeling well
10 years
10 years I see and can you see these numbers on the blackboard here
OK look at your eyes
please let me take a quick
OK
thank you
One more check here how many fingers am I holding up
No no it's only one figure OK
I just need to check your temperature
Forgotten my thermometer
could you take your mask off please and open your mouth